<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Visual Computing Reports</title><link>https://visualcomputing-2022-2.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/</link><description>Recent content on Visual Computing Reports</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://visualcomputing-2022-2.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://visualcomputing-2022-2.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/ames/ames/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://visualcomputing-2022-2.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/ames/ames/</guid><description>Ames Ilussions # Adelbert Ames Jr. # Adelbert Ames Jr. (August 19, 1880 – July 3, 1955) was an American scientist who made contributions to physics, physiology, ophthalmology, psychology, and philosophy. He pioneered the study of physiological optics at Dartmouth College, serving as a research professor, then as director of research at the Dartmouth Eye Institute. He conducted important research into aspects of binocular vision, including cyclophoria and aniseikonia. Ames is perhaps best known for constructing illusions of visual perception, most notably the Ames room and the Ames window.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://visualcomputing-2022-2.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/illusions/illusions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://visualcomputing-2022-2.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/illusions/illusions/</guid><description>Illusions # &amp;ldquo;Stepping Feet&amp;rdquo; Motion Illusion # It was demonstrated by Stuart Anstis in 2003.
The edges of the light ‘foot’ merge with the light bars and are only visible when they traverse the dark bars. So, half of the time there really is no motion cue, and perception goes into default, i.e., no motion. For the dark foot the same holds, only at alternate times.
With reduced contrast of the grating, equiluminance of edges and grating is no longer present, so the effect disappears</description></item><item><title/><link>https://visualcomputing-2022-2.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/masking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://visualcomputing-2022-2.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/masking/</guid><description>Image Kernels # What is a Convolution? # In image processing, convolution is the process of transforming an image by applying a kernel over each pixel and its local neighbors across the entire image.
The Convolution Process involves those two steps.
It places the Kernel Matrix over each pixel of the image, multiplies each value of the Kernel with the corresponding pixel it is over. Sums the resulting multiplied values and returns the resulting value as the new value of the center pixel.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://visualcomputing-2022-2.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/shaders/shaders/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://visualcomputing-2022-2.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/shaders/shaders/</guid><description>Shaders uwu # Glitch Effect Shader # Basado en el código de este video La idea del shader es tener un offset para la coordenada en x donde se dibuja el R y el B. Presione r para limpiar el canvas
Si se limita y varía el offset con el tiempo, se tiene el efecto de &amp;ldquo;glitch&amp;rdquo; Presione r para limpiar el canvas
Ascii Art # Ascii art visual application:</description></item></channel></rss>